{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Philippine Popular Culture",
    "Term": "Prelims",
    "Title": "First and Second Module",
    "LastModified": "17 May 2024",
    "Authors": [
      ""
    ],
    "References": [
      "Any external links/handouts should be referenced here"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "What are three popular culture milestones that existed among ancient societies?",
      "answer": "wedding ceremonies, music, and fashion",
      "choices": [
        "death ceremonies, music, and fashion",
        "wedding ceremonies, music, and fashion",
        "music, art, and lifestyle",
        "fashion, trends, and music"
      ],
      "reference": "Second Quiz",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "What era did Western composers began to commit their music into paper and share it to other musicians?",
      "answer": "Renaissance",
      "choices": [
        "Baroque",
        "Renaissance",
        "Industrial Age",
        "Modern Age"
      ],
      "reference": "Second Quiz",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "What culture stems from the ideas and tendencies of the working class to sort out the ones that shall be kept for their importance and consumer value?",
      "answer": "Pop Culture",
      "choices": [
        "Pop Culture",
        "Folk Culture",
        "High Culture",
        "Mid Culture"
      ],
      "reference": "Second Quiz",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "What fashion trend was happening around the Medieval period in the West?",
      "answer": "Aristocrats and the royalty began to wear clothes that took these pieces of clothing beyond functionality; the working class began to emulate these outfits.",
      "choices": [
        "Aristocrats and the royalty began to wear clothes that took these pieces of clothing beyond functionality; the working class began to emulate these outfits.",
        "Fashion was determined by cultural caste."
      ],
      "reference": "Second Quiz",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the English playwright whose works bridged both fine art and popular art, making his works appeal to many?",
      "answer": "William Shakespeare",
      "choices": [
        "William Shakespeare",
        "John Ronald Reuel Tolkien",
        "William Hemsworth",
        "Williams Shucks"
      ],
      "reference": "Second Quiz",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "What period in history did globalization start to occur?",
      "answer": "The Age of Exploration",
      "choices": [
        "The Post-Modern Age",
        "The Age of Exploration"
      ],
      "reference": "Second Quiz",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "What illegal drug almost ruined China because the British voyagers introduced it to their black market?",
      "answer": "Opium",
      "choices": [
        "Opium",
        "Marijuana",
        "chocolate",
        "strawberry"
      ],
      "reference": "Second Quiz",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "What substance, previously used in Mesoamerican rituals, became an instant hit to the European market due to the upcoming slave trade boom?",
      "answer": "chocolate",
      "choices": [
        "chocolate",
        "vanilla",
        "chocolate",
        "strawberry"
      ],
      "reference": "Second Quiz",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "What canal was completed that allowed the Philippines the access to the popular cultures of the West, which included novels, knowledge, and music, among other things back in the 1860s?",
      "answer": "Suez Canal",
      "choices": [
        "Grand Canal",
        "Suez Canal",
        "Pasig River",
        "Marikina River"
      ],
      "reference": "Second Quiz",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a solemn rite dedicated for two (2) humans to form a pact between them to love each other and make their lives work as one -- usually under the providence of their preferred deity?",
      "answer": "Wedding",
      "choices": [
        "Wedding",
        "Bar Mitzvah",
        "Engagement",
        "Blood Pact"
      ],
      "reference": "Second Quiz",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who referenced Raymon Williams in defining word --culure--?",
      "answer": "Raymond Schuck",
      "choices": [
        "Raymond Schuck",
        "Raymond Gates",
        "Andrew Clover",
        "Aristotle"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It itself is a way of living.",
      "answer": "culture",
      "choices": [
        "culture",
        "tradition",
        "belief",
        "values"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is the only thing that makes a group of people a part of culture.",
      "answer": "if they agreed to observe it",
      "choices": [
        "if they agreed to observe it",
        "if they agreed to participate",
        "if they have similar values",
        "if they accept norms"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Example of culture:<BR>Each class is divided into different social -cliques- with each clique having their own shared hobbies, conversations, and agreed norms.",
      "answer": "THE STATEMENT IS TRUE .",
      "choices": [
        "THE STATEMENT IS TRUE .",
        "THE STATEMENT IS FALSE ."
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "If you try to exclude yourself with other --tribes-- in your classroom, you will know the difference between your --social tribe-- and you classmates.",
      "answer": "THE STATEMENT IS FALSE .",
      "choices": [
        "THE STATEMENT IS TRUE .",
        "THE STATEMENT IS FALSE ."
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who defined culture as --the best that has been thought and said in the world.--",
      "answer": "Matthew Arnorld",
      "choices": [
        "Matthew Arnorld",
        "Raymond Shuck",
        "Raymond Williams",
        "Pyotr Tchaikovsky"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Matthew Arnold feared that since working-class men began to enter politics,his idea of culture might collapse since anarchy is not behind.",
      "answer": "THE STATEMENT IS TRUE .",
      "choices": [
        "THE STATEMENT IS TRUE .",
        "THE STATEMENT IS FALSE ."
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shuck's perspective is considered a vital point in studying culture.",
      "answer": "THE STATEMENT IS FALSE .",
      "choices": [
        "THE STATEMENT IS TRUE .",
        "THE STATEMENT IS FALSE ."
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "His point of view suggests that his view is an elitist perspective",
      "answer": "Matthew Arnorld",
      "choices": [
        "Matthew Arnorld",
        "Raymond Shuck",
        "Raymond Williams"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "J-pop, visual kei, anime and crazy-upbeat local commercials are icons from which country?",
      "answer": "Japan",
      "choices": [
        "Japan",
        "Philippines",
        "South Korea",
        "The United Kingdom"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "The Beatles, Spice Girls, Doctor Who, Mr.Bean are icons from which country?",
      "answer": "The United Kingdom",
      "choices": [
        "The United Kingdom",
        "Canada",
        "The United States",
        "Australia"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Elvis Presley, the Marvel Cinematic Universe, Vogue, Ted Bundy, and Coen Brothers are icons from which country?",
      "answer": "The United States",
      "choices": [
        "The United Kingdom",
        "Canada",
        "The United States",
        "South Korea"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Che Guevara is an icon from which country?",
      "answer": "Cuba",
      "choices": [
        "Cuba",
        "Philippines",
        "Mexico",
        "India"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "These are the three major spectra of culture.",
      "answer": "folk, popular, high",
      "choices": [
        "folk, popular, high",
        "tradition, values, virtue",
        "folk, traditions, values",
        "low, high, horizontal"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "This culture spectrum is what we usually associate with intelectual discourse, high-brow comedy, and elaborate literature.",
      "answer": "high culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It reflects the best aesthetics of a particular society.",
      "answer": "high culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Wolfgang Mozart's The Magic Flute is an example of what spectrum of culture?",
      "answer": "high culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Gitanjali by Rabindranath Tagore is an example of what spectrum of culture?",
      "answer": "high culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Lucresia Kasilag's Philippine Scenes is an example of what spectrum of culture?",
      "answer": "high culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Pyotr Tchakovsky's The Nutcracker is an example of what spectrum of culture?",
      "answer": "high culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is an opera compsed by the late Austrian composer Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart based on the libretto made by Emanual Schikaneder.",
      "answer": "The Magic Flute",
      "choices": [
        "The Magic Flute",
        "Gitanjali",
        "The Orchestral music Philippine Scenes",
        "The Nutcracker"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is one of the many Western compositions that reflect the best aesthetics in terms of orchestration and storytelling.",
      "answer": "The Magic Flute",
      "choices": [
        "The Magic Flute",
        "Gitanjali",
        "The Orchestral music Philippine Scenes",
        "The Nutcracker"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a colelction of poems which talks about man's beliefs and spirituality, written by Rabindranath Tagore.",
      "answer": "Gitanjali",
      "choices": [
        "Pilandok",
        "Gitanjali",
        "The Orchestral music Philippine Scenes",
        "The Nutcracker"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It utilizes the Philippines' fold musical intruments and includes some vocal noises.",
      "choices": [],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is one of many important cultural heritages of India.",
      "answer": "Gitanjali",
      "choices": [
        "Pilandok",
        "Gitanjali",
        "The Orchestral music Philippine Scenes",
        "The Nutcracker"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "These elements invoke a sense of locality we Filipinos reminisce about during festivals and viewing local sceneries.",
      "answer": "The Orchestral music Philippine Scenes",
      "choices": [
        "The Magic Flute",
        "Gitanjali",
        "The Orchestral music Philippine Scenes",
        "The Nutcracker"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a famous Christmas ballet perfomed worldwide.",
      "answer": "The Nutcracker",
      "choices": [
        "The Magic Flute",
        "Gitanjali",
        "The Orchestral music Philippine Scenes",
        "The Nutcracker"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It was compsed and written by Pyotr Tchaikovsky.",
      "answer": "The Nutcracker",
      "choices": [
        "The Magic Flute",
        "Gitanjali",
        "The Orchestral music Philippine Scenes",
        "The Nutcracker"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is so iconic; many people associate Christmastime with watching it.",
      "answer": "The Nutcracker",
      "choices": [
        "The Magic Flute",
        "Gitanjali",
        "The Orchestral music Philippine Scenes",
        "The Nutcracker"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is roughly described as something shared first in a certain gorup of people before being diseminated to the general population.",
      "answer": "folk culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It means traditions, music, and anything else practiced by a certain group is exclusively theirs until they share it with the rest.",
      "answer": "folk culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "When traced to its old Norse-English-German origin, describes an army or a small group of people.",
      "answer": "folk",
      "choices": [
        "folk",
        "pop",
        "high",
        "virtue"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is stable over time as long as people practice it but remains variable across geohraphies.",
      "answer": "folk culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "These give us a rich diversity and a plethora of regional and ethnic music, way of living, and beliefs, among practices.",
      "answer": "different regions and ethnicities",
      "choices": [
        "different regions and ethnicities",
        "diverse regions contribute unique musical traditions",
        "ethnicities bring their own belief systems, rituals, and spiritual practices",
        "regional festivals showcase vibrant customs, costumes, and rituals"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Paruparong Bukid, Atin Cu Pung Singsing, and Leron, Leron Sinta are examples of what spectrum of culture?",
      "answer": "folk culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dances such as Tinikling, Singkil, and Pandanggo sa Ilaw are examples of what spectrum of culture?",
      "answer": "folk culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Festivals such as Ati-Atihan, Higantes, and Sinulog are examples of what spectrum of culture?",
      "answer": "folk culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Folk icons such as Malakas and Maganda, Pilandok and various mythological gods and entities are examples of what spectrum of culture?",
      "answer": "folk culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It encompasses the intellectual and sophicticated aspects of culture.",
      "answer": "high culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It represents the exlusive representation of culture.",
      "answer": "folk culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is the middleman among the specturm of culture.",
      "answer": "popular culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is also called mass or mainstream culture in some references.",
      "answer": "popular culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is defined as the collection of traditions and material culture of a particular society.",
      "answer": "popular culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It can only be as timeless as the prople who know them -- if no one knows about it nor can access them, its essence fades.",
      "answer": "popular culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is sometimes called low culture.",
      "answer": "popular culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is anything that the general population can access easily.",
      "answer": "popular culture",
      "choices": [
        "high culture",
        "popular culture",
        "folk culture",
        "tradition"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Popular culture is simply a culture that is widely favored by few people.",
      "answer": "THIS STATEMENT IS FALSE .",
      "choices": [
        "THIS STATEMENT IS TRUE .",
        "THIS STATEMENT IS TRUE ."
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Popular culture is whatever is left after you have identified what --high culture-- is",
      "answer": "THIS STATEMENT IS TRUE .",
      "choices": [
        "THIS STATEMENT IS TRUE .",
        "THIS STATEMENT IS TRUE ."
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "What definition of popular culture argues that popular culture is considered inferior because of its accessibility.",
      "answer": "Popular culture is whatever is left after you have identified what --high culture-- is.",
      "choices": [
        "Popular culture is simply a culture that is widely favored (or well- liked) by many people.",
        "Popular culture is whatever is left after you have identified what --high culture-- is.",
        "Popular culture is folk culture, something that arises from people rather than imposed upon them.",
        "Popular culture can be defined as commercial objects that are produced for mass consumption by non-discriminating consumers."
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "What definition of popular culture argues that popular culture is authentic (created by the people) instead of commercial (thrust upon them by commercial enterprises).",
      "answer": "Popular culture can be defined as commercial objects that are produced for mass consumption by non-discriminating consumers.",
      "choices": [
        "Popular culture is folk culture, something that arises from the people rather than imposed upon them.",
        "Popular culture is simply a culture that is widely favored (or well- liked) by many people.",
        "Popular culture is simply a culture that is widely favored (or well- liked) by many people.",
        "Popular culture is negiotiated."
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "What definition of popular culture argues that users are free to embrace some manufactured content, alter it for their own use, or reject it entirely and create their own.",
      "answer": "In the postmodern world (i.e., today), the distinction between --authentic-- versus --commercial-- is blurred",
      "choices": [
        "In the postmodern world (i.e., today), the distinction between --authentic-- versus --commercial-- is blurred",
        "Popular culture is simply a culture that is widely favored (or well- liked) by many people.",
        "Popular culture is simply a culture that is widely favored (or well- liked) by many people.",
        "Popular culture is negiotiated."
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a category of Popular Culture?",
      "answer": "trends",
      "choices": [
        "sports",
        "news",
        "lifestyle",
        "trends"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It encompasses varied forms of media, but it usually includes television, film, music, and literature.",
      "answer": "entertainment",
      "choices": [
        "entertainment",
        "lifestyle",
        "sports",
        "news"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "This category covers any new trend that people perform and/or consume, including fashion, art, dance, language, and food trends.",
      "answer": "lifestyle",
      "choices": [
        "entertainment",
        "lifestyle",
        "sports",
        "technology"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "This covers anything related to traditional sports, including printed merchandise and icons and electronic sports.",
      "answer": "sports",
      "choices": [
        "politics",
        "technology",
        "sports",
        "news"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "This category covers any news event that has gained significant attention -- intenional or otherwise, positive or negative, which has shaped public opinion about it.",
      "answer": "news",
      "choices": [
        "politics",
        "lifestyle",
        "sports",
        "news"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "This category encompasses anything and everything politics-related, which includes politicians and political events.",
      "answer": "politics",
      "choices": [
        "politics",
        "lifestyle",
        "sports",
        "news"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "This category encompasses new media forms, inlcuding social media, gadgets, video games, and general internet culture.",
      "answer": "technology",
      "choices": [
        "technology",
        "politics",
        "lifestyle",
        "sports"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "This category overlaps with with sports in terms of eSports and entertainment because of social media.",
      "answer": "technology",
      "choices": [
        "technology",
        "politics",
        "lifestyle",
        "sports"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the three subsets of culture?",
      "answer": "subculture, counterculture, and co-cultures",
      "choices": [
        "subculture, counterculture, and co-cultures",
        "folk culture, pop culture, and high culture",
        "traditions, values, and virtues",
        "folk culture, pop culture, and low culture"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a particular culture contained in a larger culture (sometimes reffered to as its parent culture)",
      "answer": "subculture",
      "choices": [
        "subculture",
        "counterculture",
        "co-culture",
        "youth culture"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Aeta culture is an example of what subset of culture?",
      "answer": "subculture",
      "choices": [
        "subculture",
        "counterculture",
        "co-culture",
        "youth culture"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Ballet culture is an example of what subset of culture?",
      "answer": "subculture",
      "choices": [
        "subculture",
        "counterculture",
        "co-culture",
        "youth culture"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Rico Mambo culture is an example of what subset of culture?",
      "answer": "subculture",
      "choices": [
        "subculture",
        "counterculture",
        "co-culture",
        "youth culture"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hippi culture is an example of what subset of culture?",
      "answer": "counterculture",
      "choices": [
        "subculture",
        "counterculture",
        "co-culture",
        "youth culture"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Punk culture is an example of what subset of culture?",
      "answer": "counterculture",
      "choices": [
        "subculture",
        "counterculture",
        "co-culture",
        "youth culture"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is formed when a certain group begins to oppose the established normas of popular culture and breaks off from the parent culture they came from.",
      "answer": "counterculture",
      "choices": [
        "subculture",
        "counterculture",
        "co-culture",
        "youth culture"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a subculture with which a person can affiliiate themselves while existing, interacting, and negotiating within a parent culture.",
      "answer": "co-culture",
      "choices": [
        "subculture",
        "counterculture",
        "co-culture",
        "youth culture"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "Filipino-American culture is an example of what subset of culture?",
      "answer": "co-culture",
      "choices": [
        "subculture",
        "counterculture",
        "co-culture",
        "youth culture"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    },
    {
      "question": "This process of soul-searching,which also affects the dynamics and structure of culture, is called ______?",
      "answer": "youth culture",
      "choices": [
        "subculture",
        "counterculture",
        "co-culture",
        "youth culture"
      ],
      "reference": "01_Handout_1",
      "term": "Prelim"
    }
  ]
}
